WhatsApp
WhatsApp的
shapes
形状
[Music] known art
[音乐]已知艺术
[Music] was generally
[音乐]一般
[Music] and back a thousand pesos
[音乐]和一千比索
I keep thinking about it, no
我一直在想，不
[Music] your perfume brings the breeze and only remains
[音乐]你的香水带来微风，只有残留
the ashes of that cigarette that you and I share
你和我分享的那支香烟的灰烬
and the embargo of his absence
和他缺席的禁运
In my mouth it stayed another night that you are not here and I can not take it anymore
在我的嘴里住了一个晚上，你不在这里，我不能再忍受了
that loneliness
那寂寞
and a mountaineer tired of seeing me beg
和一个登山者，厌倦了见我乞求
when will he return
他什么时候回来
a tigress of light miranda
轻米兰达的母老虎
that the dawn looks tired of waiting
黎明似乎厌倦了等待
not
不是
when it was [Music]
当它是[音乐]
michael froman dominican republic disney fusion
迈克尔·弗罗姆（Michael froman）多米尼加共和国迪斯尼融合
twenties tics
二十年代
and music]
和音乐]
If I tell you that they give you everything for my time but as a boy you want to see what
如果我告诉你，他们给了我所有的时间，但是作为一个男孩，你想看看
even if you come with him then and before those tricks that for that reason it has been a long time
即使您和他一起来，并且在那些花招之前，由于这个原因，已经有很长的时间了
It is not only that I fall in love with her innocent face, I fall in love, she is a devil
我不仅爱上了她无辜的脸，我爱上了，她是一个魔鬼
well beaten and hungry fell in love does everything that lives and I already fall in love
遭受挫败和饥饿的人坠入爱河，它所做的一切生活，我早已坠入爱河
and he has already thought that he cannot be contained and the hours
他已经以为自己不能被束缚，时间
it happens to us and I love you so let me fall and mind the
它发生在我们身上，我爱你，所以让我跌倒，介意
caffeine from my heart that I fall in love with his little face and he does not let me fall in love is
咖啡因从我的内心深处让我爱上了他的小脸，他不让我坠入爱河是
a well-dressed devil you will love me accepted where I live and I already fall in love
一个衣冠楚楚的恶魔，你会爱我，被我住的地方接受，我已经坠入爱河
2 heart without a face goes like this
2没有脸的心就这样
[Music] and I've already told myself that you get complex
[音乐]，我已经告诉自己，你变得复杂
your image [Music]
您的图片[音乐]
and interest without makeup
没有化​​妆的兴趣
And if you are fat or skinny, all that does not matter to me
如果你胖还是瘦，那对我来说都没关系
I'm not perfect either or did he complain that not like this
我也不完美，或者他抱怨不是这样
[Music] and the heart has no face there is you
[音乐]内心没有面孔，有你
I promise that it is not just a cava at the end and love lives in the soul nor
我保证这不仅是最后的腔，爱生活在灵魂中，
with a wish you know that nothing to throw my forehead a peel resane goodbye the
带着希望，你知道没有什么能把我的额头丢到果皮上的宿醉
elegance is that we have if not all of them light a candle and ask for forgiveness
高雅的是，如果不是所有人，我们都点燃蜡烛并请求宽恕
because it was that you are I dedicate this song to you
因为那是你，我把这首歌献给你
If you are with the brand, all that does not matter to me
如果您是这个品牌的人，那对我来说无所谓
I am not perfect either, it is only decreed that not like this
我也不完美，只是命令不这样
tells me
告诉我
i [Music]
我[音乐]
And if you are fat or skinny, that does not matter to me
如果你胖还是瘦，那对我来说没关系
I'm not perfect either, I just know that I don't like that
我也不完美，我只知道我不喜欢那样
[Music] and the heart has no face there is you
[音乐]内心没有面孔，有你
I promise that the solcá will end
我保证solcá会结束
[Music]
[音乐]
and little else ah
还有别的啊
yes [Music]
是的[音乐]
[Applause] [Music]
[鼓掌] [音乐]
loving you like I love you is complicated [Music]
像我爱你一样爱你很复杂[音乐]
and think how I think about your sin
想想我如何看待你的罪过
look how I saw you is not prohibited
看我怎么看你不被禁止
touching you as I want is a crime [Music]
想要抚摸你是犯罪[音乐]
and I don't know what to do to make you good if you turn off the sun to turn on your
而且我不知道如果你关掉太阳打开你的身体怎么做才能使你好起来
dawn is missing and Portuguese learn to speak French or lower the moon to your
黎明不见了，葡萄牙语学习了讲法语或把月亮放下
feet I just want to kiss you and give you my mornings
脚，我只想亲吻你，给你我的早晨
sing to calm your fears I want you to not miss anything I just want to give you a
唱歌来平息你的恐惧，我希望你不要错过任何事情，我只想给你一个
kiss with my love
用我的爱吻
take you to know [Music]
带您认识[音乐]
you're welcome [Music]
不客气[音乐]
that you do not lack anything you never saw it
你不缺少任何你从未见过的东西
[Music]
[音乐]
I just want to give you a kiss and give you with my love him
我只想给你一个吻，给你我的爱他
[Music] I just want to kiss you
[音乐]我只想吻你
[Music] but I want you fascinated
[音乐]但我想让你着迷
to help is thanks my people my in what's love the kitchen
帮忙的是感谢我的家人，我对厨房的热爱
[Music]
[音乐]